(Space Rice Cake)
(Leaving their beloved Goheung behind, )
(they arrived in Seoul.)
(With their fierce ambition, they conquered Seoul...)
(and made a glamorous opening for Space Rice Cake's 2nd branch.)
(Along with its grand exterior, it features a larger kitchen...)
(filled with upgraded equipment.)
(On the 2nd floor, you'll find an expanded dining area.)
(Overwhelmed by the massive scale, the members were having a meltdown.)
(To help the members manage the shop, )
(Manager Kwon's special training began.)
(Beef burger)
(Shrimp burger)
(Mint carrot cake)
(The eye-popping flavor...)
(that makes you hum)
(The Seoul branch menu has been completely mastered!)
(8 hours have passed since they clocked in amidst the chaos.)
I can't make up my mind.
- Can we prep something now?
- I think we can make...
- wasabi mayonnaise.
- We can do that tomorrow.
Can we just make the sauce before going home?
(Therefore, today...)
We should make basil mayonnaise...
- and wasabi mayonnaise.
- What were you trying to say?
- It won't take long.
- Which one takes a long time?
- It won't.
- Wait. Hold on a second.
- Yes?
We have to...
We forgot about tteoksagna.
(Laughing in disbelief)
Oh, tteoksagna?
Since I have to make tteokbokki tomorrow,
I have to prep for it. I have to make broth.
(Additional prep 2: Tteokbokki)
(They're working late tonight!)
- Working all day long - Oh, yes.
All day long
- I'm going to go get it - Saving my knees
Red, red
Gosh, I'm tired.
What?
(They just started working, and she's already grumbling.)
Saving my knees
- Red, red - Red, red
- Celery, celery - My knees
Green, green
POS system, POS system, green, green
Hand-writing, hand-writing
- Red, red - Red
Standing up, standing up
- Red, red - Yes, yes
Sitting down, sitting down
- Green, green - Green, green
(The labor songs these days express resentment.)
Hang in there, Prince.
Thank you, Queen.
- Should I call her "Mom?"
- "Mom?"
- It should be "Mother."
- Right, "Mother."
(The Tteokbokki Prince is oblivious to the rules of the palace.)
Chef, can't we just have some fun while doing the prep work?
- Shall we make it fun?
- Yes.
- Who's your bias? I'm your bias - I'm your bias
- Who's your bias? I'm your bias - Who's your bias?
- I'm your bias - Let's lower the key.
And instead of a recent song,
let's sing an old song. From a long time ago...
(She changes the song while stuttering.)
We'll go with an old song.
Here we go. I'll go first.
Tonight
I'll send you the firefly
- From that day - From that day
(Stop)
When will this be done?
Dinner rush, and then breakfast rush
Then prep for the next morning
The next rush, breakfast rush, dinner rush
(In the end, she went back to her specialty.)
When will this be done?
Chef Mimi, should I prep all of this celery?
Yes, eight in total. I need eight stalks of celery.
Got it.
(Meanwhile, Chef Mimi is focused on chopping potatoes.)
That's ten.
- Yes.
- Twelve.
(She skipped 11.)
Who has minced garlic?
- Tell me if you have minced garlic.
- Here it is.
- Keep a notepad nearby...
- Thank you.
and make a tally mark every time you finish chopping one.
(Chuckling in embarrassment)
(Humiliated)
Young Ji, can you count the potatoes for me while I chop?
I don't understand... Can you repeat it just once?
She asked us to count the potatoes while she chops.
How does it even work?
I need to read your mind, don't I?
I'm not feeling my best right now.
Where is a wok? Oh, it's down there.
So I skipped a number while counting.
I was wondering what you meant.
(Eun Ji doesn't seem to be feeling her best either.)
(Chuckling faintly)
(Watching Eun Ji on autopilot right in front of her)
(She looks like an office worker ready to clock out.)
- You're on autopilot, aren't you?
- A little bit.
- I just need a spoon.
- I'll bring you a spoon.
I'll use this.
- Mimi, let me use the sink.
- Sure.
Young Ji looks like she's aging in dog years every day.
I think she's burned out.
How can I be burned out every day when I haven't burned myself out?
This is great. I just love my life.
The head chef's constant groaning is totally killing my vibe.
I said it was great!
You said that with a sigh. You didn't sound convincing at all!
There's nothing wrong with sighing,
inhaling, or exhaling.
Say it again, but in a happy tone this time.
Gosh, I'm so happy.
- I'm not doing this.
- I'm not doing this either.
- Just wire me my money.
- Do whatever you want.
Just send me my paycheck.
- How much is your paycheck?
- Send me my paycheck.
We didn't even make enough money for two shares of SK Hynix.
What can we even do with that money, you brat?
Did you just call me "brat?" Did you?
"Brava."
- Did you say "brava?"
- Brava.
- Then it's fine. I'm sorry.
- Oh, no.
Shall I help you measure that?
Can you prep the other ingredients?
- Leave it there.
- Thanks.
Thank you for doing the dishes, Queen Eun Ji.
- Exactly. Thank you, Eun Ji.
- Thank you so much.
- It's all so we can go home early.
- She's like a fairy.
You're sexy.
- She's perfect wife material.
- Yes, she is.
Men are lining up around the block to marry her.
Come on. Stop it.
Who will marry a woman like you? I, Kwak Cheol Yong, will marry you.
Oh, come on. Seriously.
I'm going to put you on the back of my motorcycle...
- and take you for a ride.
- I told you not to ride that.
That elegant lady used to be a total heartbreaker.
I don't break anyone's heart. I make them laugh.
She just keeps a smile on her face...
- while dancing and singing.
- Oh, come on.
I just dance because I'm excited.
- They're just amazing.
- Exactly.
- I have so much respect for them.
- Really?
Can you check the broth for me?
- Where is it? Here?
- Yes.
- It needs to boil a bit longer.
- Right? I thought so.
The aroma of the broth reminds me of Goheung.
- Really?
- Oh, the broth.
That's not good.
I suddenly feel sad again.
- I think we're done.
- Good job, everyone.
- See you tomorrow.
- Running a business is hard.
I'm so tired.
(Current Time: 11:20pm)
- Yu Jin, will you be okay driving?
- Of course. I'll be fine.
- Eun Ji, I'll take the other side.
- Okay.
- Yes. Give it to me. I'll...
- Thank you, Yu Jin.
Don't mention it. I like driving.
- You just can't help but groan.
- I'm glad you still like driving.
She must be tired from working all day long.
- There's a tteokbokki place there.
- We have some competition.
- It's us against them.
- It's right over there.
How much are they selling their tteokbokki for?
- You really have to stay on trend.
- I don't know why I'm so tired.
- It's understandable.
- Right?
We're exhausted, both mentally and physically.
We did the Met Gala all morning and then made rice cake burgers...
- all day long after that.
- That's right.
- We had no time for a break.
- Mr. Kwon was waiting for us.
- Manager Kwon.
- Exactly.
It all happened so fast.
(Their eventful day finally comes to an end.)
(Eun Ji and Mimi's room)
Dear me. My back and legs hurt.
Gosh, my back hurts.
(Laughing)
(Stretching just to stay alive)
- Mimi, it's still fun, isn't it?
- Yes.
- It's tiring, but it's still fun.
- It's fun, indeed. It's enjoyable.
(Young Ji and Yu Jin's room)
(Yu Jin went to sleep first.)
(Young Ji finished showering.)
(She spots Yu Jin.)
(Closing the door quietly)
(She carefully slips into bed to avoid waking Yu Jin.)
(So she falls asleep.)
(Snoring)
(Our head chef must've been really tired.)
It will officially begin tomorrow.
As soon as we get there, I should prep potato cream tteoksagna...
and sticky rice cake for tteoksagna.
I need to prep the desserts tomorrow.
- I see.
- I didn't prep the desserts at all.
Tomorrow will be a long day. It seemed really tiring.
Exactly. I'll get right on that first thing tomorrow.
You didn't see a POS machine in the kitchen, did you?
There isn't a POS machine in the kitchen.
Exactly. So do we have to call out the orders to you every single time?
I'm curious about how that works.
We should talk about it tomorrow.
The serving system is so high-end. I don't think I can handle it.
- So is the kitchen.
- I know, right? It's so fancy.
(The night of anxiety has passed.)
(Downtown is full of life on this bustling Sunday.)
(The bright sunlight welcomes a brand new day.)
(Today is the grand opening of the 2nd branch.)
(What will happen at the 2nd branch?)
(Space Rice Cake seems popular these days.)
(Current Time: 8:50am)
- Yu Jin, Young Ji isn't up, is she?
- No.
I'll wake her up.
(Knocking)
Your Majesty.
- Yes?
- Please forgive me for waking you.
Your Majesty.
You need to wake up now so that we can go to work.
(Walking with short steps)
- Your Majesty.
Did you enjoy a peaceful slumber last night?
- May I offer you some arginine?
- Did you enjoy...
No, that's okay.
- Your Majesty.
- Your face... Who are you?
Your Majesty, you snored so loudly...
earlier this morning.
- I'm sorry.
- You must've been tired.
- No problem, Your Majesty.
- It's all right.
- Hearing you snore...
- Yes.
- makes me happy.
- Please wake up and come out.
- Okay.
(Very well. You may all withdraw now.)
Three thousand people are tracking the waitlist on CatchTable.
- Pardon?
- Three thousand.
Oh, three thousand?
(The reservation system opened on the grand opening day.)
(About 3,000 people are waiting to book a table.)
(3,182 users are tracking the waitlist!)
They're tracking the waitlist right now?
- When does it go live?
- At 10am.
So are they going to book a table as soon as it goes live?
(The popularity of the shop doesn't feel real.)
Young Ji, 3,000 people are...
tracking the waitlist on CatchTable right now...
to swoop in at 10am when it goes live.
(The head chef shudders under pressure.)
I want to go home.
- Can you handle 3,000 tables?
- Let's go home. It's now or never.
Oh, boy. What do I do?
- How about I try to book a table?
- Go ahead.
The number of current users is 3,825.
Why would there be 3,825 people...
- waiting to book a table...
- It'll keep going up until 10am.
I'm terrified.
How come a staggering 3,825 people are...
waiting to book a table at our restaurant?
How come so many distinguished people are...
interested in our restaurant?
I'm getting so nervous.
- Eun Ji, I'm nervous.
- Me too.
(Don't worry. Even if you fail, you guys should still go.)
It's 10am now. Is it open yet?
(Current Time: 10am)
(Reservations are now open.)
- My gosh. It's already over.
- What?
(All tables are fully booked in a flash.)
Exactly. What's going on? I clicked the button.
But it said it was already fully booked.
"You have failed to reserve a table."
Eun Ji, it's over.
- I'm speechless.
- My goodness.
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Are you all mentally prepared for today?
- There's a cap on table bookings.
- That's right.
- Above all...
- I'm thrilled by the attention.
- Above all, I'm grateful.
- Right.
- Today is Sunday, right?
- Yes.
- Yeonhui-dong is packed on Sundays.
- My point exactly.
Why is today Sunday?
- Why is it Sunday?
How come it's already Sunday?
- That's exactly my point.
- When did we start?
- I've totally lost track of time.
- Me too.
I think we started last Saturday or Sunday.
Has it been over a week since we started working on this?
It's been about a week.
(It's been exactly a week since they started the business.)
- Almost a week.
- Wait. What is that waiting line?
- No way. That can't be.
- No way.
(An endless line stretches out in front of the Earth Arcaders.)
- No, that can't be.
- No way.
(They're so flustered that they can only say, "No way.")
- Seriously?
- It's not what you think.
- No.
- No, right?
- Right?
Why is everyone lining up?
- It seems like there are...
- Something must be happening.
many stores and events here.
- Honesty, humility, ahk.
- Humility, ahk.
- Nice.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
We're going to work.
I don't want to work.
What did I do to deserve having to go to work?
(Going to work while groaning)
We got rice cakes from the HQ.
(Now that they've become a major franchise...)
Girls, let's bring in the rice cakes.
Okay, Eun Ji.
One, two, three.
(They'll be delivered to their doorstep every day.)
- Shall we take them to the pantry?
- Yes.
Let's go to the pantry first.
(These rice cakes are freshly made today.)
It's heavy, Your Majesty.
(We'll introduce sponsored items from the HQ other than rice cakes.)
Good morning. This is...
the last glimpse of me looking decent today.
(Showing off her decency)
(Perk 1, the uniform)
Hello, customer.
- Would you like to order?
- My gosh.
You look like the magical...
I like this shirt.
I look like someone who works at a burger place overseas.
So today, I'll wear a waist apron...
so the shirt is more visible.
(Perk 2, POS system)
We'll go and take a look at the POS system.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- Hello.
I made a reservation through CatchTable.
- Is it a reservation for two?
- That's right.
Okay.
Take a look at our menu...
and tell me what you think.
- I'd like...
- Yes?
Too much rice cake in a burger
One shrimp burger set.
One moment, please.
(A customer who knows the menu names suspiciously well)
- Is it just 1, not 2?
- Yes, just 1.
All right, ma'am.
This is a little painful.
(The POS system isn’t as easy as it seemed.)
- Please hurry.
- Okay.
I'm starving.
I waited for a long time.
Why did I have to wait when I made a reservation?
One zesty pomegranate ade,
one do you like mint? of carrot! cake,
and one too much rice cake in a burger, shrimp. Is that right?
- Yes. I'll pay by card.
- All right.
Please give me my table number.
Thank you. Hurry up. I'm hungry.
(It seems like there's a long way to go.)
You can do this.
It's much more convenient.
(Starting prep for the new menu at the revamped 2nd branch)
Let's go.
(Keeping themselves clean at the 2nd branch as well)
Keep smiling, everyone.
Okay.
Evil spirits, go away!
- Stay away, evil spirits.
- Let's keep it beautiful.
(Irony of sending off evil spirits with "fire" on her forehead)
(The head chef starts by making the rice cake bun.)
(Placing the mold on top of gijeongtteok)
(Putting her weight onto it and pressing down firmly)
Give it one final good twist while pressing down.
That's perfect.
It's perfect.
I'll take it now.
Since it leaves some scraps behind,
- Okay.
- it's fun to cut them.
The zero-waste style.
(They're used in the carrot cake instead of being thrown away.)
(Shaking)
Like in TWS's song, you have to be a little whiny.
(Whining)
Like this.
Then it comes off.
(Whining)
(It's awkward, but it's surprisingly effective.)
Can someone call TWS for me?
That'd make me happy.
Am I not enough?
- What?
- Am I not enough for you?
Gosh, that came out wrong.
I'm really cute, you know.
Of course.
(Yu Jin is cute.)
Come on, Cheol Yong.
I thought you only liked me, but you flirt with everyone.
I didn't know you were here, Jeong Hye.
- Goodness.
- Oh, no.
I'm hurt.
(Kwak Cheol Yong is a heartbreaker.)
Shall we kiss?
(Offering an appeasement that has no chance of working)
I don't want to kiss you.
(Sulking)
You keep slipping right out of my hands.
My Jeong Hye, shall we kiss?
How about we go to Portugal someday,
fix up an old house, and live there?
But first, you have to kiss me.
Then everything will fall right into place.
My goodness.
Nothing will move forward...
if you won't even hold my hand or kiss me.
You're so naughty.
- Shall we kiss first?
- Goodness.
Are you two kissing again?
If you work well today, I'll think about it.
Thank you, Jeong Hye. You're a fox.
I'm a fox with no tail.
- Overdrive.
- You're a wolf with no tail.
You make me overdrive.
(After all that lovers' quarrel)
I finished making all the gijeongtteok for today.
- You're the best.
- Including the batch for dinner.
(Fully prepped with rice cake buns to keep going through dinner)
(Next is making the patties.)
About this much is 170g.
(She starts dribbling the beef patty with both hands.)
It looks like a basketball.
(Giving it a nice, neat shape at the end)
(All she has to do is repeat this process dozens of times.)
There's no soul in the chef's eyes.
(When the head chef feels empty inside, )
(it's time for the sous chef's shrimp patty beat.)
We are martial arts masters.
This is all part of our training.
(Training in progress)
(The shrimp patties made by a martial arts master)
(Chopping the shrimp...)
(and grinding them)
(Shape them nicely into round patties)
(Flour)
Shrimp patties should cost over 13 dollars.
- More is coming. Excuse me.
- Go ahead.
(When coated evenly, the shrimp patty prep is complete.)
(The dessert team is preparing the carrot cake.)
Making sponge cake crumbs...
from scratch is a lot of work.
I keep looking for the store-bought ones.
(Making sponge cake crumbs by hand)
(Yu Jin is shaping the carrot rice cakes.)
(When the beautiful orange dough is shaped this way and that, )
(the carrot rice cakes that look just like real carrots are ready.)
(Our cute, little carrots)
(I'm going to fry you all up)
(Somebody, save me!)
(With everything prepared)
They look like real carrots.
(Deep-fry the carrot rice cakes until they become plump.)
(The carrot cake is ready.)
I'll make some pomegranate ade now.
Did you cut the onions?
(Eun Ji practices making the pomegranate ade.)
They're over there.
(Adding plenty of sweet pomegranate syrup)
- I...
- How do you do it?
(A full cup of ice)
(Giving it a nice, refreshing chill)
(Pouring in plenty of sparkling water)
(Top it with a sprig of rosemary, and it's done.)
(Mimi, our resident sweet-tooth, gives it a taste.)
The syrup is delicious.
(The younger members take a sip.)
It looks so good.
The syrup is good.
- Eun Ji, this is amazing.
- Do I just chew it?
You can chew and eat it.
(Nodding)
Gosh, this is insane.
This syrup is good. I should buy some for myself.
- The syrup is insanely good.
- Eun Ji, it's good.
I can taste the scent of Goheung right now.
You can smell Goheung because of the pomegranate?
Yes.
(The pomegranate ade is approved.)
Everyone, it's 1:00pm.
- We're opening.
(The 1st day of business at their 2nd branch)
We are open.
- We are.
- We can do this.
Honesty.
- Humility. Ahk.
Here we go.
I'm nervous.
(With her heart fluttering, she goes towards the door.)
(Peeking)
(Meanwhile, the floor manager returns after checking upstairs.)
What's this? "Too much rice cake in a burger?"
- What?
- What's too much rice cake...
in a burger?
(Too much rice cake in a burger)
(Beef slid in)
(The service team is busy practicing the names of the new menu items.)
(Let us introduce the menu at our 2nd branch.)
(Beef burger)
(On top of a perfectly golden rice cake bun)
(A thick, juicy beef patty)
(And basil mayonnaise for extra flavor)
(Shrimp burger)
(On the perfectly fried shrimp patty)
(The kick comes from spicy wasabi mayonnaise.)
(Both burgers are available as a combo.)
(Mint carrot cake)
(With deep-fried carrot rice cake)
(A little shovel-spoon for detail)
(Bringing everything together)
(Pomegranate ade)
(A touch of Goheung)
(Original tteokbokki)
(Potato cream tteoksagna)
- I'll toast the buns in advance.
- Okay.
(The kitchen team is extremely nervous.)
(She decides to toast the rice cake buns first.)
(Buttering the heated griddle)
(Placing rice cake buns on top)
(The rice cake buns take quite a while to brown nicely.)
Is this CatchTable?
(Checking the reservation list)
Ten minutes, twenty minutes.
Thirty minutes.
Thankfully, our guests are arriving...
- every ten minutes.
- Right.
(Gasping)
Are they here, Yu Jin?
They're taking photos in the front.
(The outside of Space Rice Cake's 2nd branch)
(While the customers take photos)
Gosh, they look good.
I'm preparing them...
- before the orders come in.
- That's a great idea.
Please make them very moist with butter.
- I put on a lot of butter.
- Like Gongdeok Jeon Alley.
I will do it like hot pot at Gongdeok Station.
- Jeon Alley.
(She's talking nonsense because she's nervous.)
(At that time, the first customers come in.)
Gosh, hello.
(We will explain how to order at the 2nd branch.)
After making the payment first,
you can head upstairs.
Please go upstairs after making your order.
A total payment of 73.7 dollars in advance.
Please take this with you upstairs.
- Take this with you.
- Thank you.
(2. The table number system is used.)
Please use the self-service station for tableware.
Thank you.
(3. Tableware and water are self-served.)
(Current Hall Status)
(3 at Table 1, 1 at Table 2)
We have an order.
One beef burger, one shrimp burger,
one original tteokbokki, one potato cream tteoksagna,
- This is insane.
- two pomegranate ades,
one diet soda, and one mint carrot cake.
- This is insane.
- Okay.
We have another order.
One too much rice cake in a burger,
- beef burger set.
- Is that one more?
- That's for Table Two.
- Okay.
Will you start by making burgers, Young Ji?
The tteokbokki will be ready in no time.
Okay.
(Starting with the tteokbokki that she mastered)
Here we go.
Thank you.
(To stay in sync, )
(Mimi starts making fried food for the tteokbokki.)
(It's time to flip the rice cake buns.)
This is chaos.
The show is starting.
All right. This is great.
This is great.
They look good, but they need to be toasted more.
Today, they look like hamburger buns the most.
(Toasting the rice cake buns is going smoothly.)
I got the hang of making tteokbokki.
(Usually, when things seem this smooth, )
They ordered a lot.
(there’s bound to be something wrong.)
It's nice that they pay in advance.
I can finally relax.
(Not so fast.)
(When they took the first order)
(We'd like...)
(one of everything.)
(A massive order leaves them flustered)
(The table they're about to make a mistake with)
(They already ordered two combos that include drinks.)
(2 ades...)
(and 1 soda)
(They're 3 people, but they paid a total of 5 drinks.)
(The service team has no idea.)
Eun Ji,
the first table ordered a lot of drinks.
They only ordered three.
A soda is included in the combo.
(She remembers it only now.)
I didn't explain it to them.
(She hurries to explain to the customers.)
Excuse me,
but a Coke is included in the combo.
Then we'll just get one ade.
Just one? I'll change your order.
- I'll come downstairs.
- I'm sorry about that.
This is our first time.
Please give me a moment.
I'm having a hard time with the POS system.
Okay.
The system is very hard to work with.
(I see.)
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
We should've told you earlier.
After changing it to one zesty pomegranate ade,
I will charge you...
- a total of 66.7 dollars.
- Okay.
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I canceled it and processed the payment again.
This is order number one. Please don't be confused.
(It's time to set the basic side dishes.)
Pickled radish.
I'm curious how it turned out. Let's stir it once.
- Yes, and we should taste it.
- Stir it lightly.
Right.
(Eating)
(Humming)
It tastes so good.
(Eun Ji also takes a bite immediately.)
(Humming)
This is so good.
Where is it?
(Washing her hands thoroughly)
(Preparing pickles for the customers)
Later, we can angle it to the side...
so that it's more visible.
- To the side?
- A little like this.
People might think that it's only one piece.
I see. Like this?
It smells so good.
(The 2nd branch's complimentary side dish, yuzu radish pickle)
(At that time, Young Ji...)
(Seoul)
(Goheung)
I'm going back and forth between Goheung and Seoul.
Tteokbokki is ready.
Please serve the tteokbokki first.
I'll serve it with the drinks.
(She starts to make the pomegranate ade.)
(Adding refreshing sparkling water to the pomegranate syrup)
(After mixing it thoroughly, )
(gently placing a sprig of rosemary)
(With the pomegranate ade)
The original tteokbokki is going out.
(Heading up to the 2nd floor)
(It's her first time serving, so she feels nervous.)
Too much rice cake in a burger
(She has to take the soda included in the combo.)
(Now she's ready to serve.)
Hello.
This is Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki.
It's a menu item from Goheung...
that we couldn't give up.
This is your pomegranate ade.
And this is yuzu radish pickle.
We made it ourselves.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
(A little late to show her love as a fan)
Seriously?
It feels like a dream I had after taking the wrong medicine.
(Starting with a bite of the original tteokbokki)
(Humming)
- This is good.
- I like it.
The squid tastes good.
Since we have tteokbokki on the menu,
we can buy more time.
Now I can make tteokbokki very fast,
so we can buy time.
Here is today's first patty.
Today's first patty.
- Did you start frying the shrimp?
- Not yet.
- You can start now.
- Okay.
(Shrimp burger set)
It's in.
(She presses down the first patty to cook it.)
(Followed by a patty for the second order)
(Flipping it boldly so that it doesn't stick)
It's great so far.
It's perfect. It's thick and plump.
There's no burger patty...
bigger than this in Seoul.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Once it turns brown, she places a slice of cheese.)
(Trapping the steam inside to cook it in the steam)
Okay.
(Mimi starts to put the shrimp burger together.)
(Laying down some fresh romaine lettuce)
(Adding the freshly fried shrimp patty)
(By the time the shrimp burger is almost ready, )
(the cheese on the patty has melted to perfection.)
Mimi, one beef patty is ready.
Okay, please bring it here.
- I'll put it on here.
- Yes, go ahead.
(Adding a slice of tomato)
(Adding arugula)
I'll give a lot of the sauce because it's delicious.
It looks beautiful.
Young Ji, you grilled it so well today.
- Ta-da.
- Is the beef burger ready?
Isn't it pretty?
(Showing off the first burger)
I'm taking one beef...
and one shrimp burger to Table One.
Table One, your food is ready.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- How was the tteokbokki?
- It was good.
- Wasn't it good?
- What type of fried food is there?
In the fried food, there's pollack.
- Pollack?
- Yes.
Actually, it's cod.
- There's also squid.
- I see.
- Actually, it's shrimp.
- Is it webfoot octopus?
- No, it's cuttlefish.
- Cuttlefish?
- It's cuttlefish.
- I see.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
Sure.
(She comes downstairs.)
Gosh, look at this.
- It's so funny.
- What's that?
Why is she posing like that?
- Look.
- What is she doing?
What happened to her?
Feel free to order when you're ready.
- Okay.
(Meanwhile, the second beef burger is ready.)
- It looks very juicy.
- It's insane.
This is for Table Two.
Okay.
(Handing it immediately to Yu Jin)
(Where is he?)
Here's your burger.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
I'll bring you a Coke.
- Would you like to order?
- Yes.
First, pomegranate ade.
- Four, please.
- Four.
A combo meal includes a soda.
Would you still like to order the pomegranate ade?
- Yes.
- Okay.
One for each of the remaining ones, please.
Too much rice cake in a burger
(Giggling)
I'm having so much fun.
(A reaction that fuels the comedian)
Beef slid in
One of them.
Too much rice cake in a burger
Shrimp pop and get plump
And one of them.
"Plump shrimp pop."
Plump shrimp pop!
That way, she tells us...
they are ordering in advance.
One Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki.
Potato cream tteoksagna.
(Doing an impression of Mimi out of nowhere)
(Bursting out laughing)
(Smiling)
(It was too much.)
I really want to go home.
Would you like one of each like this?
- The cake.
- We'd like one cake.
- Cake.
- Mint carrot cake.
Please sign it.
- Everyone, - Enjoy your meal.
- please wait upstairs.
- Okay.
- We have an order.
- We heard the entire order.
- Okay.
- That's great. A big order.
(However, Eun Ji missed something.)
They forgot to take it with them.
I was supposed to take it upstairs.
- You two, sit on the other side.
- Okay.
(A number sign is needed for serving.)
I was supposed to take it upstairs.
I forgot to bring it to them.
Let's go. You can do it.
(Problem 1: She forgot the number sign.)
Yu Jin, I have to bring it to them,
- so could you give me one?
- Okay.
(Meanwhile, the next customers come pouring in.)
- Would you like to order?
- Yes.
Okay.
You definitely look like fans of "Earth Arcade."
- Inside the burger, - Yes?
is there mayonnaise?
In the too much rice cake in a burger, there's mayonnaise.
- I'll ask.
- Okay.
Is it possible to leave out the mayonnaise sauce?
If they can't eat it, I can leave it out.
Then there won't be any sauce in the burger.
Can you leave it out only from the beef burger?
Only from the beef burger?
- Would you like your receipt?
- Yes, please.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(Problem 2. She forgets the number sign again.)
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin goes to serve.)
- Here's your dessert.
- Thank you.
(She gives number 4 to the table without a number sign.)
(Current table numbers)
(Numbers 1, 2, 4, and none)
(The remaining orders: Table 4)
(Unnumbered Table)
Here we go.
(Starting with the beef patty for Table 4)
(And she adds the rice cakes.)
- They love the original tteokbokki.
- Really?
Who am I? I'm Lee Young Ji. I'm the master of tteokbokki.
(A quick moment to show off)
(Immediately followed by making patties)
(Chef Mimi slices the rice cake buns...)
(and takes out fried food for the tteokbokki.)
(Thanks to her work, the original tteokbokki is made fast.)
Tteokbokki for Table Four is ready.
(The beef burger is also ready.)
Eun Ji, I'll serve the beef burger and the original tteokbokki.
Okay.
(Table 4: 1 shrimp burger combo)
(While Mimi is busy working on the shrimp burger)
Take a look at that.
Is the tteoksagna...
- ready?
- Potato cream tteoksagna?
Potato cream tteoksagna? Okay.
(It takes the longest to make potato cream tteoksagna.)
They're eating everything on the menu.
(She's in a hurry, and the cooking is complicated.)
- You can do it.
- This is nice.
This is wonderful.
(Piling up by grinding it carefully)
(She finally opens the oven.)
(Hustling to finish the tteoksagna)
Eun Ji, be careful. It's hot.
(10 minutes remain starting from now.)
(Problem 3: Missing an order item)
(She takes out the shrimp patty right away.)
(Delivering it before it cools down)
- The shrimp burger is ready.
- Okay.
(Next, Yu Jin goes to squeeze on the ketchup.)
It's for the person who ordered the beef burger.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- Oh, no.
- It's too burnt. I'll take it out.
(Problem 4: Overcooking)
We have an order of four pomegranate ades.
(Adding pomegranate syrup)
(Adding ice)
(Pouring sparkling water)
(Mixing well)
(Placing the rosemary)
This menu item is hard to make.
(On top of that, the next customers arrive.)
Hello. Please wait one moment.
Would you like to look around the pop-up store?
I'll go and serve pomegranate ades.
Go ahead.
I'll come back right after serving these.
(Excellent floor management)
Here's your zesty pomegranate ade.
Did you harvest the pomegranate too?
Did we harvest the pomegranate? That'd be suicidal...
(We'll stop there.)
(Meanwhile, the customers in the waiting zone)
Look at that.
(Flustered by Young Ji who turned into garaetteok)
- Look at that.
- That's cute.
(Welcome)
(They also find the photo zone inside.)
(Imagine being on the moon.)
(There's a mirror for selfies on the ceiling.)
Can you come inside?
- Am I in the frame?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
(They gather up for a selfie.)
(While they enjoy their time together)
Let me know when you want to order.
- Shall we order first?
- Okay.
- What would you like?
- Shall we get these three?
- That's good.
- Two pomegranate ades, please.
- Okay.
- And one carrot cake.
- You're Table Five.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
We have another order. Please check.
(Remaining Order Status)
(At that time, in the hall...)
(Taking a big bite of a beef burger)
It's good.
(Eating)
(Lost in the rice cake burgers side by side)
(Cleansing the palate with the yuzu radish pickle)
It's really refreshing.
- Gosh.
- It's really nice.
- It's very good.
- Yes, it tastes good.
I like garnishes like this.
(At the next table, they start with tteokbokki.)
It's good.
Young Ji has an old-school palate.
Like a tteokbokki shop in front of an elementary school...
- back in the day.
- Right.
(Its original name was kiddie tteokbokki.)
(She takes a bite of the burger next.)
(Exclaiming)
- Isn't it like a rice burger?
- Rice burger?
It's exactly like a rice burger.
It's delicious.
(While the customers enjoy the food peacefully)
I have so much to do.
(When the girls get busy)
Potato cream tteoksagna? Okay.
I'll prepare the cheese and the potatoes.
(It's time for multiplayer Yu Jin to step in.)
We need two servings of tater tots.
Do I just cover the fish with frying mix?
(The perfect example of knowing what to do)
Yu Jin, could you take out the fried food?
Put it on top.
Yu Jin, can you cut this for me?
Sure, I'll try.
This is hard.
(Sighing)
What should I do about this?
- Are there three of you?
- Yes.
(The POS system gives her a hard time.)
(The orders come in endlessly.)
It's very confusing because we're not used to it.
We can't meet in person like in Goheung,
so we can't communicate.
We need to figure out a solution.
(Let's run away!)
That one is without mayonnaise, right?
Yes.
If you set a bun without mayonnaise, I'll put the patty.
(Moving a juicy beef patty)
- I'll put the burger together.
- Okay.
You have so much to do, Mimi.
(Taking over the burger assembly for busy Mimi)
(Awkward)
(On top of a fresh slice of tomato)
(Refreshing arugula)
(Lastly, she fixes it with a burger pick.)
It's ready. It's the one without mayonnaise.
- Tteokbokki is ready.
- Okay.
(Unnumbered Table: 1 original tteokbokki)
The original tteokbokki is ready.
(Food for the Unnumbered Table is ready.)
(Yu Jin who has no idea goes to serve.)
(She checks the order.)
(2 pomegranate ades, 1 mint carrot cake, 1 original tteokbokki...)
(It says Table 5.)
(Going up while taking it at face value)
- Is this Table Five?
- We didn't get any number.
You didn't? But is this Table Five?
- I guess so.
- It should be.
- We aren't sure either.
- I'll go and check.
Okay, thank you.
We just came upstairs, so I don't think it's for us.
(Tilting her head)
- We just arrived.
- I'll go and check.
(Then she has an idea.)
Are you the one who can't eat mayonnaise?
- That's right.
- It's us.
Here you go.
(Thankfully, the food found its owner.)
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
(Off to deliver the bad news)
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
The receipt says number five,
- but it was placed somewhere else.
- What do we do?
What should we do about it?
How should we solve this...
- Does it say five on the order?
- No.
The one who can't eat mayonnaise is number five.
Could you modify it so that...
- we can understand?
- This is...
Number Five, and this one is Unnumbered Table.
(The service team organized it on their own.)
(Finally, the tteoksagna that was omitted gets ready.)
Be careful, Eun Ji.
I'll take it out for you.
(Decorating it with rosemary)
(Sprinkling some parsley too)
(Eun Ji also makes the pomegranate ade.)
For which table is the potato cream tteoksagna?
Number four and...
Number four and pomegranate ade.
Are you Table Four?
We didn't get any number.
- I see.
- Be careful.
Didn't you order potato cream tteoksagna?
- No.
- Is this not for you?
- How about two pomegranate ades?
- Yes.
Here are your two pomegranate ades.
Thank you. I forgot to give you a table number. I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
Table Four?
(In plain sight)
It's so good to see you.
(Laughing)
- The food is delicious.
- It's absolute chaos.
- Is it good?
- The rice cakes are...
really good.
- The rice cakes are amazing.
- Really?
Enjoy your food.
Table Four.
(They thought...)
(having a POS system would solve everything.)
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
- Look. When you go over there...
- Yes.
We don't give them numbers in order.
- If it's 6, this is also 6.
- It's 6.
After picking the number, you write the same number.
- That's a relief.
- Do you get it now?
It gets confusing if you just follow the numbers.
- We have to remember the people.
- Once we get that down,
- everything falls into place.
- Right.
Two cakes need to go out. Can you do that, Yu Jin?
- We have one cake.
- We have one here.
- Then I'll go and serve.
- I'll prepare something else.
We finished serving two tables.
(She hurries over because she made a mistake.)
- Shrimp burger.
- Thank you.
- This is your carrot cake.
- It's so beautiful.
Shall I put this underneath to make it pretty?
- Sure.
- That'd be better.
(Even if she makes mistakes, she takes care of her customers.)
- Did you all get your sodas?
- Yes.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
(Looking so delicious that it begs for a photo)
I want one too.
(After taking photos of the food, )
Are they looking good?
(they take a photo together to celebrate the moment.)
Let's eat.
(Remaining Order Status)
(Tteokbokki, shrimp burger, tteoksagna)
I'm going to make a potato cream tteoksagna.
Okay.
(After laying down a sheet of baekseolgi, )
(she adds a generous amount of the potato cream sauce.)
(Now, it's time to add cheese.)
(Piling a generous amount of mozzarella)
(Then she stretches sticky rice cake...)
(and places it like a blanket on top of it.)
(Then she covers it with the ragu sauce.)
(Another layer of mozzarella)
(After grating some Parmigiano, )
(it's ready to go into the oven.)
(While waiting for 10 minutes, )
I'll put them to the side.
(Young Ji toasts rice cake buns they were running out of.)
(She preps the fries for tteokbokki without a problem.)
(Yu Jin gets ready to set the rice cake burgers in advance.)
(She fries the tater tots in advance too.)
(Ketchup)
(After Yu Jin sets the sauce, )
(Mimi assembles the burgers.)
(From freshly fried shrimp patty...)
(to crunchy onions!)
Shrimp burger is ready.
Hot behind.
Tteokbokki is ready.
(The original tteokbokki is ready too.)
Hold on.
Please set the mat because I didn't place it yet.
(Placing)
I'll take the original tteokbokki and the shrimp burger first.
Okay.
(The customers in the meantime)
When you work, snacks can help you a bit.
- It helps a lot.
- I got some.
Do you need one of my chocolates?
If you use your body and brain every day...
all of a sudden...
(Pushing)
(Grabbing)
(Earth Arcaders' snacks are gathered little by little.)
(But this one is worried only about not messing up the orders.)
Here are your orders.
- Thank you.
- This is very hot.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- This is the pickle we made.
- Did you make it yourself?
- Yes.
Okay. Thank you.
Here are two zesty pomegranate ades.
Gosh. Thank you.
One of them is different.
(The perfect reaction)
Please shove it in here.
- Come on. Stop it.
- Gosh.
Goodness. Really.
Mix it well...
- and enjoy it with the seeds.
- Okay.
Thank you.
(Thanks to them, she's recharged.)
(Checking again to see if they missed anything)
- I crossed out the original.
- The shrimp is served too.
- Did you serve the shrimp? Good.
- Excuse me.
We're only missing tteoksagna.
Okay. The carrot rice cake can be served with tteoksagna.
It should be served with tteoksagna.
Tteoksagna...
It's ready now. I'll give it to you.
Be careful.
(While it gets cooled down, )
(Yu Jin grabs a cup for the dessert.)
(First, add a layer of yuzu marmalade.)
(Then tear gijeongtteok on top of it.)
(Fluffy gijeongtteok over refreshing yuzu marmalade)
(Then goes the mint cream.)
(Adding a fun texture with the crumbled sponge cake)
(Portraying dirt with cocoa crumble)
(Carrot rice cake is the highlight.)
(Decorating the orange fried sticky rice cake with rosemary)
(After sticking it into the cocoa crumbles, )
(a shovel-shaped spoon is placed for the final touch.)
- Here is the carrot cake.
- It's cute.
(A new dessert, mint carrot cake!)
Okay. With these, we're done with Table Five.
Here's your potato cream tteoksagna.
- It's hot, so be careful.
- Okay.
My lovely princesses.
- Here's the carrot cake.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
- It's pretty.
- It's Torong's favorite.
- Gosh. No.
- What's on the bottom?
- It's mint and... What's that?
Yuzu?
- I think it's yuzu marmalade.
- It's...
(All dishes have been served.)
(Next customers are entering.)
Hello.
Was it served?
- What is your name?
- Chae Mi Hyeon.
Chae Mi Hyeon. Please wait.
We have new orders.
A zesty pomegranate ade, a mint cake,
a potato cream tteoksagna, a Young Ji's original tteokbokki,
a shrimp burger combo, and a beef burger combo.
(One of all dishes on the menu)
- Let's go.
Honesty, humility, ahk.
- Ahk.
- Do it super fast.
(The big order has them scrambling.)
(Placing the patty quickly)
Something great will happen today.
Something amazing will happen.
(The kitchen is full of energy.)
- The reservation is under Li Wei.
- Yes. It's Wei Li.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from China.
- I see. "Ni hao."
- "Ni Hao."
(Space Rice Cake has its first foreign customers now.)
My name is Lee Eun Ji. Thank you.
(The floor manager has no problem welcoming the foreigners.)
Your Chinese is really good.
- Was it okay? Thank you.
- Yes.
Everything is going so smoothly as if it's a fast-food chain.
I seriously think we're faster than McDonald's.
(Grilling a patty while bragging)
That's right. I'm serious.
(The beef patty is ready at a chain-restaurant speed.)
I'm not kidding.
Those patties from today can go into my filmography. Seriously.
(Lee Young Ji's filmography: Winner of "High School Rapper 3,")
(Winner of "Show Me the Money 11," and 2026 Beef Patty Master)
Please spread some mayo for me, Mi Hyun.
- Mayo? Basil mayo?
- Yes.
- I'll assemble it.
- Okay.
(Piling up the ingredients)
(After placing the well-grilled rice cake bun, )
- The beef burger is ready.
- Okay.
(the beef burger is ready.)
(At the hall in the meantime)
But why isn't our dessert coming?
(Table 4: 1 Mint carrot cake)
- Is that it?
- Yes.
(Table 4: 1 Mint carrot cake)
(They're enjoying the carrot cake.)
Yes. That's it.
(The customers who arrived after Table 4)
Yes. Good.
- You can have the carrot.
- I'll have the mint.
What are you doing?
(They're all enjoying the desserts.)
Let's ask when they come back.
When they come back, we can ask.
(And on the 1st floor, )
(one dessert is waiting to be served.)
We need two cakes, Yu Jin.
- Can you handle it?
- There's one here.
One cake is ready already.
(Table 4: 1 Mint carrot cake)
Here's the shrimp burger.
(Unnumbered Table: 1 shrimp burger combo, 1 mint carrot cake)
Two tables are all served with their orders.
(The dishes for the two tables were served at once.)
Here's the shrimp burger.
(They were all served to Unnumbered Table.)
And here's the carrot cake.
- It's pretty.
- Thank you.
I think they went downstairs after getting them the dessert.
(Just like that, Table 4...)
(is missing their dessert.)
(Yu Jin has no idea.)
Is this served or not?
(She's confused about the remaining carrot cake.)
(She grabs it and brings it to the 2nd floor.)
Here are your beef burger and pomegranate ade.
(Table 3: 1 pomegranate ade, 1 beef burger combo)
The bun is made of rice cake.
Who made this?
This? Young Ji made it.
(The beef burger and the ade are all served.)
- Please enjoy.
- Thanks.
(She leaves with the carrot cake.)
(There must be a table missing a carrot cake.)
(Looking around)
Wait. Here.
I think that's ours.
We didn't get our carrot cake yet.
Ta-da.
(The customers are satisfied with her cute performance.)
Please enjoy.
(She charmed her way out of trouble.)
- There's mint in it.
- Isn't the carrot rice cake?
Isn't this the rice cake?
- It's well made.
- Yes. I know.
Yes. It's good.
It's cute. It even has a shovel.
(Fortunately, Table 4 is happy with the dessert.)
It's cute.
We have new orders.
One Young Ji's original tteokbokki.
One too much rice cake in a burger combo.
One zesty pomegranate ade.
- Mi Hyun.
- Yes.
When did you make this shrimp patty?
Just now.
- I'll assemble it.
- I just made it. Okay.
(Making the shrimp burger first with the freshly fried patty)
(Slicing open the rice cake bun)
- About this much?
- Add a moderate amount of onions.
The shrimp burger is ready.
(After placing the freshly fried fries)
Great timing.
A small original tteokbokki is ready.
Once the potato cream tteoksagna is ready,
- one table will be finished.
- Okay.
(The tteoksagna will be ready soon.)
The tteoksagna.
- Okay.
- Here's potato cream tteoksagna.
(On her way to find the customers)
- Seriously.
- It's really good.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
The bowl is really hot.
- Please don't touch it.
- Okay.
Your hands are more precious than my life.
- Thank you.
- We ordered so much.
Our customers should enjoy warm and tasty dishes.
That's our priority.
I add the fries when it's boiling vigorously.
(Boiling vigorously)
(The head chef adds the fries...)
(when tteokbokki is boiling vigorously.)
- Okay.
- It's hot.
(The sous chef carries the patty from the fryer by hand.)
It's kind of exhilarating.
- How so?
- When it's hot.
- Here's the shrimp burger.
- Okay.
Here's the tteokbokki.
(As the dishes are getting ready consecutively, )
(the service team has to hurry.)
Here's your shrimp burger.
- Here's the carrot cake.
- It's cute.
It's hot. Don't touch it.
(They don't forget to warn that it's hot.)
(They also provide a lunch show.)
(Amazed)
Thank you.
Gosh. The shrimp burger is good.
(Satisfied)
It's tasty.
The shrimp patty is so plump.
It's really good, though.
(While the customers enjoy their meal, )
(they're reorganizing the kitchen after serving all the dishes.)
Why is it so slow today?
I shouldn't say something like that.
(You're right. It brings in a customer.)
I'll get your orders now.
(Yu Jin welcomes the 1-person customer.)
Gosh. I should throw away this apron.
Why?
- I hate this apron.
- You need a long one.
We should switch our aprons.
Wear this one, Your Majesty.
- Okay. I'll tear it apart.
- It's the longer one.
- Tear those aprons apart.
- Don't tear them apart.
What is this?
Don't say you'll tear them apart.
Just put it over this one.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Seriously.
- Why?
- This is crazy.
- Orders are in.
- It's time for some fun.
- Okay. Orders are in.
- Okay.
- We have new orders.
Okay.
One Do you like mint? Of carrot! Cake.
Too much rice cake in a burger One shrimp burger.
Okay.
(Order Status: Shrimp burger, carrot cake)
(Tteokbokki is missing.)
Gosh. We have plenty of time.
Please go and ask...
if they want tteokbokki.
Why? Do you feel sad because they didn't order it?
I'm sad. I want to serve them tteokbokki.
(Sure. I'm coming to order the tteokbokki.)
One Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki, please.
(Even the secondary hall is packed at Space Rice Cake.)
- I'll make the shrimp burger.
- Good.
(Mimi assembles the shrimp burger.)
I can keep making tteokbokki.
I can even make six at once.
- Goodness.
- It's hot. It was just fried.
Amazing. Our customers will love it.
Yes. It's incredible.
It's best right after frying.
(Yu Jin squeezes the mint cream into the cup...)
(to make the carrot cake.)
Everything is going smoothly.
- The service team is a great help.
- That's right.
(She goes to serve the last dish.)
- Done.
- Good job.
(The kitchen team finishes cooking.)
(And the customers get ready to leave.)
Thanks for the food.
- Yes. Safe trip home.
- Did you enjoy it?
(The head chef goes to send off the first customers.)
How did you like it? Be specific.
- It was great.
- Tteokbokki was so good.
Tteokbokki was good. What about the burgers?
How were the burgers?
I liked the shrimp burger.
Did you like the shrimp burger?
How did you like it? Be specific.
- It was great.
- Tteokbokki was so good.
Tteokbokki was good. What about the burgers?
How were the burgers?
I liked the shrimp burger.
Did you like the shrimp burger?
Okay. Wishing you a long and healthy life.
You must be thrilled as the shrimp burger is popular.
The beef burger can't be just so-so.
(They never said it was so-so.)
(Sad novice chef's 4 stages of emotions)
My beef burgers are just fine.
(Stage 1: Denial)
I have no problem.
This? Do you think this is ordinary?
(Stage 2: Rage)
Get me the leftovers.
Don't eat the leftovers.
They said the beef burger wasn't good.
Honestly, they didn't say it wasn't good.
- Mimi.
- Yes.
They said the beef burger was so-so.
- I don't know.
- It's not so-so.
- That can't be true.
- I don't know.
It can't be ordinary.
Our sauce is so good.
But they looked like they were sick of it.
How so? Show me.
"The beef burger was..."
(It's based on Young Ji's distorted memory.)
What should I do?
I gave my all to the beef patty.
What a waste of my life.
Jeong Hye, my poor life!
- Jeong Hye!
- It's my first time too.
(Cheol Yong, it's my first time running a restaurant too.)
(Cheol Yong feels better thanks to Jeong Hye.)
Darn it.
Bye.
- We enjoyed it.
- Thanks.
- We love you.
- We enjoyed it.
Did you have tteokbokki?
- Tteokbokki was so good.
- Really?
Did you have a beef burger too?
- Yes. It was so good.
- Was it good?
Thank you.
(I really needed to hear that.)
(Smiling again)
- Gosh. Lunch business was great.
- Good job.
- Well done.
- Goodness.
(They've finished lunch business in Seoul without any problems.)
Mi Hyun, please flip the sign.
(Space Rice Cake)
(The sign is flipped to "Closed.")
Yes.
(Get home safely.)
Let's go.
(Space Rice Cake)
They must be wondering what we're doing.
(Current Time: 2:54pm)
(They're done with lunch service.)
- We need to prep. For two hours...
- Yes.
No. We'll rest for an hour.
Then we'll prep vigorously for an hour.
How many hours do we have?
(They have about two hours until dinner hours.)
(The aftermath of the lunchtime is massive.)
We have to go upstairs and clean up.
(They start cleaning up.)
Got it, girl.
Yu Jin, do you think I can carry these?
You can do it, Eun Ji.
(With a chant, they muster up the last bit of their energy.)
(She can handle it)
I need to empty the oil container.
(Wiping)
(Wiping again)
Gosh. This is not a break, is it?
No, it's not.
- Leave it here.
- Okay. Thanks.
Sure.
- I'm always grateful.
- Sure.
I love you, Cheol Yong.
I love you, Jeong Hye.
(The love lives on while it's a bit emotionally dry.)
They finished the whole tteoksagna.
I'm so proud.
(Though they're little worn out, they are proud.)
This is cute. Look at this.
Right.
"We enjoyed the meal. Space Rice Cake."
- "Good luck."
We enjoyed cooking them.
Space Rice Cake,
- good luck.
- Good luck.
(Propelled by customers' warm support, )
(they finish cleaning up.)
(Checking the lunch sales)
(It makes them clap.)
I need to tell Young Ji right away.
(The 1st business at the 2nd branch)
(Revealing the lunch sales)
(5 beef burgers: 69.50 dollars, 8 shrimp burgers: 119.20 dollars, )
(7 tteokbokki: 83.30 dollars, 4 tteoksagna: 52 dollars, )
(6 cakes: 48 dollars, 11 ades: 33 dollars, 1 soda: 2 dollars.)
(Total sales: 407 dollars)
There was a customer who came alone,
- but we still made this much.
- Exactly.
We'll reach 1,000 dollars today after dinner.
It's 3:07pm right now. Isn't it better to eat quickly...
- and start prepping?
- Yes. Let's eat quickly.
What should we do? Lunch boxes?
- Lunch boxes sound good.
- Do we have lunch boxes?
(Current Time: 3:30pm)
(They have gimbap for lunch in the pantry.)
It's good.
Do you want to know how much we made?
Yes.
Was it 430 dollars? Was it 400 dollars?
That's good.
Fill up your stomachs.
I think dinnertime will be a real challenge.
The pomegranate ade is a problem.
- Right, Eun Ji?
- Yes.
- Everyone orders it.
I think they all ordered it because that was the only drink we had.
- The meal is served with a soda.
- Okay.
But some wanted the pomegranate ade.
We got both orders of soda and pomegranate ade.
That's why they couldn't finish either of them.
So, if it's possible...
For an extra 50 cents,
- they can change it to the ade.
- They can get the ade instead.
Wouldn't that be better?
(For an extra 50 cents, they can get the ade.)
(They start prepping for dinner after finishing their lunch.)
After finishing the lunch service,
I sat outside for five minutes.
Then I had a few pieces of gimbap...
before getting ready for dinner.
After I wipe the griddle...
And do you remember how tteokgalbi was a bit bland?
So I need to add more sauce.
Then our...
Jeong Hye washes the dishes thoroughly.
Jeong Hye's in a trance.
She's completely lost in washing dishes.
The dishes never end.
- It just never ends.
- It doesn't end.
But of all people, she's best at it.
She's fast too.
I used to work part-time in many places.
I worked at a pork cutlet place too.
While working at the pork cutlet place,
I briefly dated the owner.
My goodness.
(She said something she shouldn't have...)
(right in front of Cheol Yong.)
It was...
It was just for a moment.
I know everything, Jeong Hye.
Do you want to know what I know?
(He only knows about love.)
(Throwing)
My brother, Byeong Cheol, the owner of the eel place.
You dated him too, didn't you?
I didn't date him.
You kissed him. But you wouldn't kiss me.
(Kiss-lover Cheol Yong is bitter about it.)
I didn't really date him.
- We just went to...
- I heard it all.
We just went to karaoke together a few times.
Why do you go to karaoke?
Because it's fun!
Did you sing "Kinky Boots," "Moulin Rouge!" and "Mama Mia?"
Did you sing those there? Just tell me.
What can I do when those are my songs?
That's how she flirts with men.
She uses that to charm all the men.
What about you?
You subtly show off your biceps when you make the patty.
Just showing your charm like that.
(The middle-aged couple is upset with each other.)
There they go again. Goodness.
From east to west
My love is everywhere
My love, Lee Jeong Hye
- Where is she?
- Lee Jeong Hye?
Did you just say Lee Jeong Hye?
Lee Jeong Hye.
I'm Sunwoo Jeong Hye.
(Goodness me.)
Who is Lee Jeong Hye?
(The middle-aged couple's final love ended in disaster.)
Lee Jeong Hye...
- Who is Lee Jeong Hye?
- Calm down.
Back when you used to work at the gas station,
you changed your name from Lee Jeong Hye to Sunwoo Jeong Hye.
Who changes their surname?
(Cheol Yong lacks common sense.)
Love isn't for everyone
- Love isn't for everyone - Love isn't for everyone
(Hoping they work it out smoothly)
(After the lovers' quarrel)
(Space Rice Cake)
- Shouldn't you start prepping now?
- I'm about to start now.
I'm spending the whole day just cleaning the griddle.
- When is the part-timer coming?
- The part-timer?
- Please.
- The part-timer...
Please.
- will come when it's time.
- Now is the time.
(First, the POS system)
(Second, high table seating)
(Third, waiting zone)
(And the part-timer...)
(who's still nowhere in sight)
Come and see, part-timer.
I'm the youngest member here.
You'll be the youngest when you come.
That's right. Yu Jin won't be...
- the youngest anymore.
- Right?
- I'll train the youngest.
- That...
- doesn't go according to age.
- Don't do anything.
- It goes according to experience.
- Sure.
The person who joins last is the youngest.
Then does the previous youngest have to teach them a lesson or not?
Come here!
(Not very good)
No. It should be like, "What do you think you're doing?"
(Demonstrating)
- What do you think you're doing?
- I'm sorry.
- Corner them like that.
Are you ready to do that?
I'm ready.
- Whoever comes, whatever the age.
- I'll do it.
What do you think you're doing?
(Playing the part of the part-timer)
Go up the stairs.
- But...
- Don't you want to go upstairs?
I came here thinking it was a TV show.
Why are you being so harsh to me?
(Variation of a past question)
- Hey.
- But...
you don't seem to be doing anything. This is so funny.
Follow me into the fridge.
(Okay.)
Haven't you heard, Yu Jin?
I'll be joining the next season for "Earth Arcade."
Hey!
(No one is more fun to tease than this youngest.)
- Why?
- You...
- That's...
- Yes?
That's my last pride.
- Really?
- Do you know how hard I worked...
to keep this post as the youngest?
I can't do anything about it because they offered it to me.
(Getting furious)
Follow me into the fridge.
Yu Jin.
I was born in 2008.
I hope you treat me well.
(It's less of a simulation and more about teasing her.)
- Take the dishwasher.
- Okay.
(The youngest is coming!)
- Yu Jin.
- Hey!
- Is it hot? It's not, right?
- It's okay. It's warm.
Okay.
Hey, youngest, clean this up.
Who's the youngest? Are you the youngest?
Youngest.
Why do you keep trying to get more people...
when I'm doing so well?
Who knows?
Employees can always be substituted.
You never know.
She might have longer legs than Yu Jin...
and act cuter than her.
She might be polite to her seniors...
and act cute as well.
Young Ji.
(Here's the cute act you ordered.)
- Are you feeling okay?
- Are we going to kiss?
No.
(Cheol Yong is always lonely.)
Cheol Yong!
(Shouting)
You should do that only with me.
But you don't.
Let me wipe this now.
What should I do now?
We have to start prepping now.
- Okay.
- Can't we rest for a bit?
Rest? Get some rest after you die.
Once we're done with lunch, we get ready for dinner.
Are you serious?
I know, right? All we did was eat, and now we have to prep.
Until when...
Isn't it horrible that lunch service wasn't too busy?
This is driving me crazy.
Dinner service is a nightmare.
I can't even imagine.
(They start prepping 40 minutes before opening.)
This looks like the color of tteokgalbi now, right?
It looks like it. You put more sauce than before, right?
- Yes. Much more.
- Nice.
I just went bold with it. I thought it should be a bit salty.
I think it would be better if it's salty.
- We have a review.
- A review!
- Girls!
- Yes?
We have a review!
(A review from a valued customer)
- I'm so curious.
- Tell us.
- The review says...
- The part-timer is so cute.
- We were given five stars.
- Five stars.
"Food tastes great, and the people are so pretty and kind."
"It was so interesting how the buns of the rice cake burger..."
"were rice cake."
"The wasabi sauce has a sharp kick that really makes it."
"The carrot cake also goes really well with mint,"
"and it was chewy and tasty."
"I had a great meal. I'd like to visit again."
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Do we have more?
- So far it's this one only.
This is the first review.
- Nice.
- Please leave us more reviews!
(After the brief joy from the positive review...)
When the part-timer comes,
tell her how to make the pomegranate ade.
Let's keep the greetings brief.
Let's just greet her with a nod.
- We'll just greet her with a nod.
- Okay.
Hold on.
And an introduction. "Hello, I'm Lee Young Ji."
Seeing that she's not here yet,
I think she'll be here at a really busy time.
Goheung feels like last year.
I see.
(It's only been two days.)
Check when the part-timer arrives. We have to pay her accordingly.
Is there an hourly pay?
Isn't this just volunteer work?
(The shamelessness of wanting an unpaid worker)
(Meanwhile, Eun Ji is done washing the dishes.)
What can I do for you?
(They're already tired even before opening.)
(She's about to faint.)
- What do you need?
- Catch your breath.
Catch your breath. Get some rest.
Get ready, and think about how you'll teach the part-timer...
how to make the pomegranate ade.
I'll teach the part-timer how to make the pomegranate ade.
- We'll just greet her with a nod.
- With a nod.
- A nod.
- Hello.
- We really don't have the time.
- We really don't.
No matter who comes in, we can't greet them.
Even if it's Beyonce,
- we can't greet her.
- We can't.
Part-timer.
Greet the camera.
There's no time to hesitate. The pomegranate ade.
Go upstairs.
- Good job.
- Yu Jin is good.
- What should we have her wear?
- We have to dress her too?
- Let's pick something.
- Do it, Yu Jin.
(Part-timer strategy simulation)
- Hello.
- Your uniform. In the restroom.
- Hello. I'm Lee Young Ji.
That's Mimi, Yu Jin, and Eun Ji.
Okay.
(The part-timer finished changing.)
I got changed.
Okay. Then make some pomegranate ades.
Okay.
Hold on.
(Passing by)
- I'm done.
- Then go outside.
Okay.
Aren't you a bit cold? Smile a bit.
- Do it again, Yu Jin.
- Hello.
Hello. I'm Young Ji.
(Laughing)
- It's scary here.
- A moment, please.
Let us rest, please.
(The prep for dinner service is almost done.)
- I'll start with the buns.
- Okay.
Please take care of me well.
It's 30 minutes.
I'll flip the sign.
- Let's go.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
(It's finally dinner service time.)
Space Rice Cake...
is open for dinner service!
(Current Time: 5:30pm)
(They made a loud opening, but there's not a single customer.)
Are there no customers yet?
That's how business goes.
When you prep hard,
- there are no customers.
- That's what I'm saying.
When you go a bit easy, then suddenly...
(Suddenly...)
That's so true.
It's hard to tell.
Why aren't they coming? They should come at exactly 5pm...
for everything to work out.
(For some reason, they don't have customers.)
- I know. You prepared for that.
- I got them prepared.
I prepared two burgers.
I'll place an order.
Are we here?
I'm so nervous.
(A car arrives in front of Space Rice Cake.)
(Her voice is shaking with excitement.)
I'm nervous.
Goodness. It's cute.
(She makes her way over with a racing heart.)
- I'll place an order.
- Hello.
(She enters with the words she practiced.)
- I'll place an order.
- Hello.
- Goodness!
What brings you here?
I heard you opened a rice cake place.
- What?
- Hello.
- The strict one.
- The part-timer?
- Are you going to pay for food?
I came to help.
- She's the part-timer.
- The part-timer!
The part-timer!
- Part-timer, come over here.
- My gosh. What was that?
- I wanted to see her face.
- Come over here.
- Come with me.
- Go on, part-timer.
- Follow me.
- Right. Show her the kitchen first.
- Here's our part-timer.
Say hi to the camera.
- Hello.
- We're in trouble.
- You took me by surprise.
Hello. It's nice to meet you all.
(A part-timer is here as they wanted.)
(Will they finally catch a break?)
(Coming up next)
(Space Rice Cake welcomes...)
(an incredibly special new part-timer!)
(The manager rushes her the moment she arrives.)
(The youngest, the disciplinarian of the group, is even stricter.)
(Thanks to her, the part-timer is completely disciplined!)
(I'm too scared to work here.)
(The work environment is definitely no walk in the park.)
(You're going way too fast with the training.)
(If you need anything, tell me right now!)
(This part-timer is no pushover.)
(4 servings? I've got this.)
(She's a quick learner.)
(Shall I serve the food?)
(Will you do that for me?)
(And she has amazing drive.)
(On top of everything, she dominates the dining area with her charisma.)
(She rises to become the indispensable ace of the team.)
(It's so good to have a part-timer here.)
(But their happiness is short-lived.)
(Table 8 is missing their beef burger.)
(Oh, they ordered 2 servings?)
(They keep missing orders.)
(Everyone, that moment has come.)
(The kitchen team grows impatient.)
(What do we do?)
(There are so many mix-ups and errors.)
(Are you okay?)
(Where did it all go wrong?)
(They launch 2 new dishes to overcome this crisis!)
(The first new menu item: Ghost pepper pizza)
(On top of the dough made from injeolmi)
(The hometown friend that they could never give up)
(Ghost pepper)
(On top of the golden brown rice cake dough)
(Adding basil leaves for the final touch)
(The chewy rice cake pizza is born!)
(It's spicy and delicious!)
(The second new menu item: Goheung sea margarita)
(This refreshing drink captures the longing for Goheung's sea.)
(It's so popular.)
(Visually stunning and delicious new menu items are coming soon.)
(Space Rice Cake)